Edward Catalanotti

System Analyst

Levittown, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Edward-Catalanotti/2b60ae625ccbfe25

EDWARD J. CATALANOTTI JR. 27 Cactus Road Levittown, PA 19057

[...] EJCat83@gmail.com

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY PROFESSIONAL

Proactive, collaborative professional with over 9 years of experience in identifying processes that improve the overall stability across system, software, and network within the telecommunications and visual arts industries. Specific expertise includes integration, system performance, maintenance, troubleshooting, research, monitoring, and equipment setup. Currently seeking an opportunity to apply skills and experience to improve product stability and user experience.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

SOFTWARE: Unix/Linux, shell scripting, Python, Hadoop, HTTPD Apache and Tomcat (operations), terminal server RDP, Voice SIP- L3 VOIP, Windows XP/Vista/7, Adobe Flash, Final Cut Pro, After Effects

FAMILIAR WITH: SQLPlus/ MySQL/ MS Access, Sun JVM - 1.5 - 1.6 BEA (oracle) JRrocket 1.5,

HARDWARE: 32 + 64 bit single and multi process backend web service platforms, (Dell + Super micro) Virtual Platform (Xen + KVM) PC and Macintosh, laptop, Smart Boards, LCD, Slide

VIDEO: Cameras (DVC Pro, Betacam SP, 24P), VCR's, VCR/DVD players

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

HEALTH ADVOCATE, Plymouth Meeting, PA 2014-

Research Associate (2014-)

Research cases generated for member in need of assistance locating physicians and locations.

Credential the physicians, find out if the physician is in-network and other information to generate a report to send to the member.

- Research the physicians that accept our members insurance.
- Credential the physician is board certified, and their license is clear and active.
- Call the physician to find out if they're accepting new patients, our in-network with the insurance, next available appointment, verify the location, contact information.
- Generate a PDF of the letter to the member with two to three different physicians. Proof read the letter before sending it to our member.

EDWARD J. CATALANOTTI JR. 27 Cactus Road Levittown, PA 19057 Page 2 HALE-SMITH INC., Morrisville, PA 2012

Internet Marketing/ Social Media Specialist (Dec. 2012-)

Manage all the housing listings on the Internet. Generate listings about to be placed on social media. Update existing listings with new information. Contact potential customers along with existing clients and resolve any issues

- Generate daily housing listings in preparation to be placed on social media. Create postings on Craigslist, Twitter, and Facebook.
- Update existing posts.
- Communicate with potential customers, third party vendors, and existing customers to resolve issues.
- Create Virtual Tours of housing listings
- Insurance Policy Endorsement

NOKIA LOCATION & COMMERCE, Malvern, PA 2007 - 2012

System Operator (2010 - Nov. 2012)

Managed traffic applications and servers throughout Nokia, ensuring that customers received traffic information in a timely matter. Generated nightly reports and made recommendations to improve performance of the systems. Collaborated with third party vendors, customers, and internal stakeholders to troubleshoot and resolve data feed issues.

- Created and stabilized production Nagios by updating Nokia configuration files to meet traffic needs. Worked with the team to migrate to physical hardware, consolidate log file monitors (from 14,000 to 2,000), address performance issues of JBoss monitors, and create/test/implement custom monitors for specific uses.
- Trained transitioning support team on all monitoring systems, procedures, and documentation. Provided back up support throughout the transition and transfer of responsibilities.
- Maintained and upgraded products within Production and QA Linux environments and Windows server subsystems for Traffic products and services. This included cleaning up disk space, restarting application, reviewing log files, and testing network connectivity. Identified performance issues with application feeds and contacted providers to alert them of issues.
- Performed 300+ quality/health checks to support demonstrations, showcase products, and services daily. Provided first-level support for 200 Map and Map Content products and services.

Shift Editor (2007 - 2010)

CREATIVE VISUAL IMAGES, Voorhees, NJ 2006 Video Assistant (Intern)

THE ART INSTITUTE OF PITTSBURGH, Pittsburgh, PA 2003 – 2004 Video Technician EDUCATION

Masters, Information Systems (MIS), The University of Phoenix, Phoenix, AZ

B.S., Digital Media Production, The Art Institute of Philadelphia, Philadelphia PA

AFFILIATIONS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Research Associate

Health Advocate - Plymouth Meeting, PA - April 2014 to Present

Responsibilities

Research cases generated for member in need of assistance locating physicians and locations.

Credential the physicians, find out if the physician is in-network and other information to generate a report to send to the member.

- Research the physicians that accept our members insurance.
- Credential the physician is board certified, and their license is clear and active.
- Call the physician to find out if they're accepting new patients, our in-network with the insurance, next available appointment, verify the location, contact information.
- Generate a PDF of the letter to the member with two to three different physicians. Proof read the letter before sending it to our member.

Internet Marketing/ Social Media Specialist (Volunteer)

Hale-Smith Inc - Morrisville, PA - December 2012 to June 2014

Responsibilities

Manage all the housing listings on the Internet. Generate listings about to be placed on social media. Update existing listings with new information. Contact potential customers along with existing clients and resolve any issues

- Generate daily housing listings in preparation to be placed on social media. Create postings on Craigslist, Twitter, and Facebook.
- Update existing posts.
- Communicate with potential customers, third party vendors, and existing customers to resolve issues.
- Generate information for new house listings to potential customers.

System Operator

Nokia Location & Commerce - Malvern, PA - November 2010 to November 2012

Managed traffic applications and servers throughout Nokia, ensuring that customers received traffic information in a timely matter. Generated nightly reports and made recommendations to improve performance of the systems. Collaborated with third party vendors, customers, and internal stakeholders to troubleshoot and resolve data feed issues.

- Created and stabilized production Nagios by updating Nokia configuration files to meet traffic needs. Worked with the team to migrate to physical hardware, consolidate log file monitors (from 14,000 to 2,000), address performance issues of JBoss monitors, and create/test/implement custom monitors for specific uses.
- Trained transitioning support team on all monitoring systems, procedures, and documentation. Provided back up support throughout the transition and transfer of responsibilities.
- Maintained and upgraded products within Production and QA Linux environments and Windows server subsystems for Traffic products and services. This included cleaning up disk space, restarting application, reviewing log files, and testing network connectivity. Identified performance issues with application feeds and contacted providers to alert them of issues.

• Performed 300+ quality/health checks to support demonstrations, showcase products, and services daily. Provided first-level support for 200 Map and Map Content products and services.

Shift Editor

NOKIA LOCATION & COMMERCE - Malvern, PA - June 2007 to November 2010

Managed 15+ employees ensuring that all shift coverage and traffic was reported on and that all necessary data was entered. Rescheduled coverage when shorthanded.

- Managed all aspects of shift; ensured all cities across US were being monitored and entered into data base with accidents, construction, congestion or other events affecting the roads.
- Troubleshot technical issues.
- Trained new employees on the cities.
- Monitored all cities uncovered due to employees absences as well as cities required for coverage by shift editor.
- · Called news stations to inform them of any closures.

Video Assistant (Intern)

Creative Visual Images - Voorhees, NJ - July 2006 to September 2006

Video Technician

The Art Institute of Pittsburgh - Pittsburgh, PA - March 2003 to December 2004

EDUCATION

Masters in Information Systems

The University of Phoenix - Phoenix, AZ

Bachelors of Science in Digital Media Production

The Art Institute of Philadelphia - Philadelphia, PA

LINKS

http://www.linkedin.com/in/edwardcatalanotti

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

AFFILIATIONS

IEEE - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers